torrentomega.com 2015-12-07

# Contactus | MagneticLink - SearchVerve.com Best DHT Search engine

### Your Privacy at Searchverve 

##### A Friendly Warning to P2P Users: 

BitTorrent is not illegal, it is just a technology. Laws are violated by people, not by computers or programs. 

Sharing (or downloading) copyright-protected content is illegal in your country. We ask you to check local laws before engaging in any P2P data transfer activities. 

P2P can help you get more help resource.but we do ask you **NOT** download or spread any copyright-protected content online. Pay attention,there are numerous companies created for this sole purpose to monitor your activities. The BitTorrent protocol (as the most of p2p protocols) connects to peers directly (every participant can see ip address another participants). For the sake of privacy you should use either anonymous proxy servers or VPN, We recommend you to use a VPN service. 

### 1\. Introduction 

SEARCHVEVE values your privacy and do not collects user information. This Privacy Policy outlines the collection, use, and dissemination of your personal information and you must agree to it in order to use our service. This Privacy Policy is the one agreed to in our Terms of Service, and forms a part of those Terms of Service. Users can opt of data collection. 

### 2 Information We Collect and Cookies 

SEARCHVEVE does not require users to register, subscribe or set up an account to use SEARCHVEVE. We use cookies to save User preferences. You can use the service without cookies. 

We do not keep any of your personal information.Server access logs are kept for 24 hours for technical reasons, then deleted automatically. Since we're using Magnet links, your downloads are never logged by us. 

We may log IP addresses and specific actions (voting and comments) of visitors for a short period of time (24 hours) to prevent spamming. Access to that data is limited, data is purged automatically. 

We may read and write HTTP cookies with user preferences and history. Cookies that we access are not linked to your personal information or IP address. 

We display non-personal data related to search queries and viewed torrents (realtime queries, search cloud, popular torrents). 

### 3\. Why We Collect Information 

SEARCHVEVE collects limited user information to enhance or improve the website, user experience and service. 

SEARCHVEVE strives to keep limited personal information secure, and we do not disclose it to any third party. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure. 

We may use 3rd-party visits tracking and advertising systems, which can store cookies in your browser. There are several ways to remove or block it if you're so concerned. We can recommend to use Incognito Mode in Google Chrome to access our site (you will not be able to store preferences / access history). 

We try to prevent misleading / malicious advertising on Searchverve. If you encounter such ads let us know (please specify URL of malicious creative and a description of problems). 

### 5\. Age Requirements 

Children under the age of 13 are expressly prohibited from using SEARCHVEVE without parental consent or guidance. 

### 6\. International Users 

SEARCHVEVE is designed to private research on DHT and P2P technology, but it open to you,If you are sent to this website by Google or Yahoo or Msn .you can share the searchengine index informations.Nevertheless, SEARCHVEVE's privacy policy is drafted to conform to the international requirements for websites. By using SEARCHVEVE, users accept (expressly and/or implicitly) SEARCHVEVE's privacy policies.Please notify us if you discover any content which is infringing on someone's rights, so we can blacklist it from index. Notification procedure is described here. 

### 7\. Amendments 

The Amendmentsparagraph of our Terms of Service is hereby incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy and applies to any amendments that we may make to this Privacy Policy.We reserve the right to update this policy at any time. Please direct any privacy-related questions
